safelinkconverter1.com 2015-02-22

# Privacy Policy | Safe Link Converter

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party  Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.>

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Use of Google Adsense For Revenue Sharing**

We use Google Adsense for revenue sharing with our Authors.So we will follow all the policies of Google Adsense on our website.

**Authors Should Maintain There Adsense Account On Their Own**

We won’t maintain Adsense account of our authors.Authors have to maintain their account on their Ownand the Authors are fully responsible for any problem related to their adsense account.So if you are banned from Adsense or don’t get your payment from Adsense we are not responsible for that.

**Revenue Sharing Percentage**

The revenue share percentage with our authors depend on their level of registration.The authors have to contact us to get information about the revenue share.

**Websites Accepted**

We accept all websites which do not contain or links to any adult content, drugs, liquor or copyrighted content .

**Copyright Protection**

Our website “Safelinkconverter.com” and its linked domains are protected by Copyright Law of State of California.  
So copying anything from our site is against our policies and its a major violation and We can are authorized to take any legal measures necessary.

**Advertisments**

_We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated infromation (not including your name, address, emal address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:[http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.as](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)_

**Payment by Us**

We only give payment to some Elite Members only from our side only if the person / company is not violating any of our polices and it not trying to cheat our system in any way. If a company / person is found doing fraud with our service / system then we can ban user , block payment , deduct the amount for fraud against our system as well as take any legal actions according to loss we incurred due the fraud done by a company / person.

We are not liable to pay according to the reports received.The final decision of sending payment depends on us.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Please keep visiting this page for any changes because you will not be notified about any changes.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://safelinkconverter.com/contact-us/

364, Sector 18-A, Dwarka, New Delhi -110078  
New Delhi, Delhi 110078  
India  
safelinkconverter@gmail.com
